## CHARUTA DANDEKARFeatured Resume

HR Manager seeking roles in Human Resource Management, Recruitment, Talent Acquisition, Compensation Management, Payroll Management, Performance Management, Talent Management, Career Planning, Employee Engagement, Employee Relation, Restructuring

Current Designation: HR Manager

Current Company: Luxora Infrastructure Pvt. Ltd

Current Location: Mumbai

Pref. Location: Mumbai

Functional Area: HR / Administration / IR

Role: HR Manager

Industry: Real Estate/Property

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Total Experience: 12 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Notice Period: 1 Month

Highest Degree: MMS [Human Resource Management]

Key Skills: HR Manager, Human Resource Management, Recruitment, Talent Acquisition, Compensation Management, Payroll Management, Performance Management, Talent Management, Career Planning, Employee Engagement, Employee Relation, Restructuring

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

ID: 393009b34911095538Last Active: 17-Sep-20Last Modified: 16-Sep-20

Jump to SectionWork Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Self motivated, hard working and goal-oriented M.M.S. (Human Resource Management), from Bharati Vidyapeeth's Institute of Management & Research (Mumbai University), with a high degree of flexibility, resourcefulness and commitment.

Currently working with Luxora Infrastructure Pvt. Ltd. designated as Manager- HR.

A team player, ability to work comfortably with people from diverse backgrounds and experiences with analytical, execution and interpersonal skills, systematic approach and quick adaptability.

Good people skills ability to communicate effectively and build long lasting/ mutually beneficial relationships.

**Work Experience** 

Luxora Infrastructure Pvt. Ltd as HR Manager

Aug 2017 to Till Date

Recruitment, generalists, Employee engagement, payroll Administration

The Calibre Services - The Concept as Talent Acquisition Consultant

Feb 2017 to May 2017

Sourcing Profiles across various industries (Includes Major R.E Cos and ensuring timely closures of Mandates.

Luxora Infrastructure Pvt. Ltd as HR Manager

Apr 2014 to Jan 2017

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Com (Commerce) from Mumbai University in 2002

PG: MMS (Human Resource Management) from Mumbai University in 2006

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

M.Com (Part I)

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used Experience

HR Align, ERP (Info Velocity)